chelseabridson

about

interests

435 N Fairview Ave Lansing, MI 48912 (517) 918 - 0717

material design, user experience, web accessibility, single page applications, mobile design, continuous integration and delivery, automated deployment, automated acceptance tests

☐ chelsea@bridson.me chelsea.bridson.me git://seadb

education

languages

native english basic spanish 12-2015 **B.Sc.** in Computer Science MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY Computer Science & Engineering College of Engineering Dean's List, College of Engineering Scholarship

2015-2016

HACKER FELLOWS

CISSP ASSOCIATE

2017

programming

Javascript/ES6 React

Redux

Angular **jQuery**

C/C++

C#

Python

CSS3

HTML5 Node

Django

SQL

Fellowship which matches developer talent with Michigan startups and includes

a 5-week entrepreneurship & coding bootcamp and stipend

Certified Information Systems Security Professional

experience

2017

2015-2016

2018-present **b Liquid Web**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Created UI mockups to confirm design meets business requirements
- Create and maintain an automated end-to-end test suite to cover basic acceptance criteria to verify business level requirements for manage.liquidweb.com

• Collaborated on a team to create a new user interface for my.liquidweb.com

• Write and maintain thorough unit tests to ensure code reliability

REACT, REDUX, GITLAB, SKETCH, SELENIUM, PERL, JAVASCRIPT

■ MSU Information Security

SECURITY ANALYST

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Web Application Management System

- Developed the WAMS internal firewall onboarding software
- Responded to support tickets and issued SSL certificates for internal servers

C#, ASP.NET, MICROSOFT SERVER, GIT

volunteering

2018 & Lansing Bike Party

2017 CLansing Bike Co-op

2016 PRoom at the Inn Warming Center

2016 **T** Food Gatherers

2015 & Common Cycle

2014 ☐ MSU Women In Engineering

2013 & EL Hot Yoga

2013 The Giving Tree Farm

2012 Ponald McDonald House Mid-Michigan

Seelio

Skills Map

• Created a user-interface for the skills map, a feature designed to help students connect soft skills to past experiences and projects

- Researched and implemented continuous integration & deployment
- Adhered to Agile bi-weekly sprint planning sessions and daily

JAVASCRIPT, BACKBONE.JS, KNOCKOUT, CIRCLECI, SELENIUM, AWS, GIT